libertyfund.org 2016-10-29

# Liberty Fund

LIBERTY FUND, INC. ("Liberty Fund", "we", or "us") recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information provided by users of our web site, www.libertyfund.org (the "Site"). We created this policy (this "Policy") with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our users. This Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Site. We may modify the Policy at any time and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your consent 

**Effective**

This Policy was last modified on April 25, 2011. 

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect information from visitors to the Site. You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card number, email address or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP number (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation, including use for industry reporting purposes. 

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your registration or orders; to administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our or third party products, services, promotional events or special offers that maybe of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. We may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other web sites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other web sites to provide advertisements on the Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If we are involved in the sale of a substantial portion of our business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information may be among the transferred assets. 

**Communications with Us**

The Site may have features where you can submit information to us (such as our feedback forms or committee interest forms). Such submissions may be made public. Requests for service, support or information may be forwarded as needed to best respond to a specific request. We may retain e-mails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better. When you send an email or submit information to us through the Site, you are communicating with us electronically. You thereby consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the Site. All agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

**Communications from Us: Service Updates, Special Offers**

In order to best serve you, we may send updates that contain important information about the Site and our services. We may also communicate with you to provide requested services and for account-related issues via e-mail, phone or regular mail. We offer you the option to receive information about our organization, related products, services and special events.

**Automatic Data Collection**

In order to best serve you, we may send updates that contain important information about the Site and our services. We may also communicate with you to provide requested services and for account-related issues via e-mail, phone or regular mail. We offer you the option to receive information about our organization, related products, services and special events.

**Privacy of Children**

We encourage parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law.

**Security**

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving your information. Additionally, we implement commercially reasonable security measures at our physical facilities to protect against loss or misuse of your information. We use Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution.

**Links to Third-Party Websites**

The Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites even if these third-party websites are listed as affiliates or as those with whom we have partnered. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information. As well, we are not responsible for the misuse of our name, products or services listed on other sites.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Beginning January 1, 2005, California law permits individuals who are California residents to request once in any calendar year certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us by email at [webmaster@libertyfund.org](mailto:webmaster@libertyfund.org), or write to us at:   
Liberty Fund Webmaster   
Liberty Fund, Inc.   
8335 Allison Pointe Trail   
Suite 300   
Indianapolis, IN 46250-1684

**Notification**

For questions about this privacy statement, or questions concerning the practices of the Site or any dealings with us contact:   
Liberty Fund Webmaster   
Liberty Fund, Inc.   
8335 Allison Pointe Trail   
Suite 300   
Indianapolis, IN 46250-1684
